Elizabeth Torralbo Valenzuela

elizabeth.torralbo.valenzuela@gmail.com

Career Summary

Hi! My name is Elizabeth and I live in Barcelona, Spain. I'm currently studying to be a Front end Developer with the SheCodes Workshops. I previously studied foreign languages and translation. I've lived in different countries and I've been working in Business Administration for the last 15 years.

Professional Skills

Business	Tech	Languages
Salesforce	HTML	Spanish
MS Office	CSS	English
Power BI	JS	French
Tableau	Bootstrap	German
SQL	Github	Italian

Work Experience

Customer Service Specialist EMEA at Keysight Technologies in Barcelona
April, 2015 - Present
Customer Service Specialist Germany at HP in Sant Cugat del Vallés
Nov, 2014 - April, 2015
International Relations Manager at Université de Grenoble in France
Sept, 2013 - Aug, 2014
Customer Service Specialist EMEA at Agilent Technologies in Barcelona
Nov, 2009 - Sep, 2013

Education

Postgraduate in Audiovisual Translation from Universitat Pompeu Fabra 2010-2011

Bachelor of Translation and Language Interpreting from Universitat

Autònoma de Barcelona

2001 - 2006